const data = [
  {
    question: "What is the function of the epithelial tissue?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Barrier, absorption, and excretion",
      "Tranformation, absorption, and secretion",
      "Immunity, protection, and absorption",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Barrier, absorption, and secretion",
  },

  {
    question:
      "A group of organized __________ working together forms __________. An organized group of the latter work together to form __________.",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "tissues; organs; cells",
      "organs; cells; tissue",
      "None of the options",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "cells; tissue; organs",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following tissue types make up the inside or outside lining of something?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["connective", "muscular", "nervous"],
    correctAnswer: "epithelial",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If you observe a layer of columnar cells of varying heights, they would be called __________ columnar cells.",
    incorrectAnswers: ["simple", "stratified", "complex"],
    correctAnswer: "pseudostratified",
  },
  {
    question: "An epithelial membrane consists of __________ tissue.",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "muscular and neural",
      "connective and muscular",
      "nervous and connective",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "epithelial and connective",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The epithelial membrane that surrounds the heart and lungs separately is called a __________ membrane.",
    incorrectAnswers: ["cutaneous", "synovial", "apical"],
    correctAnswer: "serous",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What type of gland is being described? Part of the actual cell breaks away in order to release its products.",
    incorrectAnswers: ["holocrine", "merocrine", "endocrine"],
    correctAnswer: "apocrine",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Lining layer of fallopian tubes, bronchi and bronchioles consists of",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Colummar epithelium",
      "Cubical epithelium",
      "squamous epithelium",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ciliated epithelium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The epithelial membrane that lines the body cavities that are exposed to the outside of the body is called a __________ membrane.",
    incorrectAnswers: ["serous", "synovial", "basal membrane"],
    correctAnswer: "mucous",
  },
  {
    question: "What the polarity of epithelial tissues",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "apical and complex",
      "simple and basal domains",
      "apical and regional",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "apical and basal domains",
  },
  {
    question: "The stoma of the body, included",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "supporting tissues only",
      "connective tissues only",
      "ducts",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "supporting and connective tissues",
  },
  {
    question:
      "A cluster apposed cells with very small amount of extracellular matrix, named",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "supporting tissues only",
      "connective tissues only",
      "ducts",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "epithelium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organized aggregation of the identical cells, specialized to perform a particular function, known as",
    incorrectAnswers: ["sheets", "bands", "cells"],
    correctAnswer: "tissues",
  },
  {
    question: "The diameter of the cilia is about",
    incorrectAnswers: ["3-8 micrometer", "2-4 micrometer", "1-5 micrometer"],
    correctAnswer: "5-10 micrometer",
  },
  {
    question: "The parenchyma of the body composed of",
    incorrectAnswers: ["cells only", "tissues only", "muscles"],
    correctAnswer: "cells and tissues",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The epithelium that contains two or more layers of the cells, referred as",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "unilaminar epithelium",
      "covering epithelium",
      "squamous epithelium",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "stratified epithelium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The epithelium that contains only single layer of the cells is named",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "simple epithelium only",
      "unilaminar epithelium only",
      "cover epithelium",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "simple and unilaminar epithelium",
  },
  {
    question: "The body tissues can be categorized as",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "epithelium",
      "connective tissues and muscular tissues",
      "nervous tissues",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of above",
  },
  {
    question: "Most organs of the body composed of",
    incorrectAnswers: ["parenchyma only", "stroma only", "ducts"],
    correctAnswer: "parenchyma and stroma",
  },
  {
    question: "Stratefied epithelium is also named as",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "unilaminar epithelium",
      "covering epithelium",
      "squamous epithelium",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "multilaminar epithelium",
  },
];

export default data;
